Y'all keep saying Israel will get the U.S. Israel and the U.S. are the same thing.
Israel and the U.S. are the same thing.
The same thing.
Please. Please.
I was where you were a year ago and then I kept paying attention and I understand now. Please.
Israel and the U.S. are the same thing.
Are the same thing.
If we're playing chess, if we're playing chess, right, and I'm on the side of the board with the white pieces, and I have a pawn and I have a rook and I have a castle, and you're on the other side, you're not saying, oh, the castle is attacking me.
You're saying you're attacking me with your castle.
Okay.
Israel and the United States are the same thing.
They are pieces on a board that are all being moved by the same hand.